[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":39346,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":72448,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":13957,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":86406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":22045,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":108452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1972,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":110426,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":6027,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":116454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1502,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":117957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second  one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":39782,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":157739,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1787,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":159526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":163509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1380,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":164889,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3518,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":168407,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub> 6</sub>  0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1592,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":169999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5091,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":175091,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1186,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":176277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br / ><br />  (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3375,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":179653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":890,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":180543,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your resu lt.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3642,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":184185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":936,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":185121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2918,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":188040,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":832,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":188873,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7","1"],"rt":5390,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":194264,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":988,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":195253,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":45060,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":240314,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inv erse und er +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":73573,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":313887,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":35568,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":349455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3196,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":352651,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br  /><br />  (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3345,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":355997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1627,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":357625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2769,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":360395,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":958,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":361353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2299,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":363653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under  +<sub>6 </sub>.","rt":1145,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":364799,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3003,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":367802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":10022,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":377824,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simp ly be pe rformed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":58261,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":436086,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</su b> 2, bu t there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":164355,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":600442,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":11017,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":611461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":4553,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":616014,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br  /> (Rem ember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4749,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":620763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":12802,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":633566,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</s ub>? <br  /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6433,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":640000,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1692,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":641693,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4919,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":646612,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":6880,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":653493,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question w ith feed back to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":50423,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":703916,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":5455,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":709372,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1519,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":710893,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3820,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":714713,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4443,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":719158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4414,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":723572,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2657,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":726229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3883,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":730113,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":13823,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":743937,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"4 + 1 = 5 and then 5 is less than 9 so that is the answer.","explanation_history":["4 + 1 +","4 + 1 = 5 and then 5 is less than 9 so thats the answer.","4 + 1 = 5 and then 5 is less than 9 so that s the answer.","4 + 1 = 5 and then 5 is less than 9 so that is the answer."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":60325,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":804263,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9.","explanation_history":["8 + 4 =9 ","8 + 4 =9","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subract 9","8 + 4 = 12 and t hen 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9, ","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9,","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9 ","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9, so t","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9, so 3 i","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9, so 3 ","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9, so 3","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9, so ","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9, so","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9, s","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9, ","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9,","8 + 4 =12 and then 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":51044,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":855308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in wo rds how  you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"because +9 is the same as +6 except for how big the answer can be and how much you subtract if its larger.","explanation_history":["because +9 is the same as +6 except for the ","because +9 is the same as +6 except for the","because +9 is the same as +6 except for th","because +9 is the same as +6 except for t","because +9 is the same as +6 except for how big the an","because +9 is the same as +6 except for how big the a","because +9 is the same as +6 except for how big the number ","because +9 is the same as +6 except for how big the number","because +9 is the same as +6 except for how big the numbe","because +9 is the same as +6 except for how big the numb","because +9 is the same as +6 except for how big the num","because +9 is the same as +6 except for how big the nu","because +9 is the same as +6 except for how big the n","because +9 is  the same  as +6 except for how big the answer can be and how much you subtract if its larger."],"response_history":["0"],"rt":85022,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":940331,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":17128,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":957460,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":4755,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":962215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 u nder +<s ub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":4663,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":966879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"3 + 6 = 9 and then 9 would be subtracted to reach the identity of 0.","explanation_history":[" ","3 + 6 = 9 and then 9 would be subtracted to reach the indentity of 0.","3 + 6 = 9 and then 9 would be subtracted to reach the identity of 0."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":53991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1020871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explai n in wor ds how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because you can't get all the numbers 1-8 with just 2","explanation_history":["because you can't get all the numbers 1-8 with just 2"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":133811,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1154682,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because you can't make all of the numbers 1-8 with just 3.","explanation_history":["because you can't make all of the numbers 1-8 with just 3."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":44098,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1198780,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":" Is 5 a g enerator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because you can't make every number 1-8 with just 5.","explanation_history":["because you can't make every number 1-8 with just 5."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":55949,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1254729,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"no, can make every number 1-8 with just 6.","explanation_history":["no ","no, can make every number 1-8 with just 6."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":17362,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1272091,"internal_chunk_id":"0- 0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":97716,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1369807,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 + x = n - 1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 + x+","1 + x","1 + x + ","1 + x +","1 + x = n- ","1 + x = n-","1 + x = n - 1"],"rt":75048,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1444856,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse  of an e lement x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n - x","explain":true,"explanation":"the inverse is going to be  whatever n is minus whatever x is because the inverse will be whatever makes x the same as n","explanation_history":["the iner","the ine","the inverse is going to be  whatever x is ","the inverse is going to be  whatever x","the inverse is going to be  whatever n is minus whatever x is because x +","the inverse is going to be  whatever n is minus whatever x is because x ","the inverse is going to be  whatever n is minus whatever x is because x","the inverse is going to be  whatever n is minus whatever x is because the inverseve ","the inverse is going to be  whatever n is minus whatever x is because the inverseve","the inverse is going to be  whatever n is minus whatever x is because the inversev","the inverse is going to be  whatever n is minus whatev er x is  because the inverse will be whatever make ","the inverse is going to be  whatever n is minus whatever x is because the inverse will be whatever makes x the same as n"],"response_history":["x =","x + 7 ","x + 7","x + y = n - x","x + y = n - y","x + y = n - x","n - x"],"rt":142193,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1587050,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm not sure , I'm still confused on this aspect.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I'm not sure , I;m still confused on this aspect.","I'm not sure , Im still confused on this aspect.","I'm not sure , I'm still confused on this aspect."],"rt":49867,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1636918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":5816,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1642735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":2759,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1645494,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub >n</sub> , x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":18157,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1663652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"1 goes into 6 an even amount of times but is still a generator","explanation_history":["1 goes into 6 an even amount of times but is still a generator"],"response_history":["False"],"rt":98450,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1762103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":11256,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1773360,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"I'm confused as to how the generators work.","explanation_history":["I'm confused as o ","I'm confused as o","I'm confused as to  how the  generators work."],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":22475,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1795836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":3990,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1799827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2415,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1802243,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"26","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["26"],"rt":2862,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1805106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":4031,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1809137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, plea se list  them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"business calculus","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["business calculus"],"rt":13049,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1822187,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3913,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1826101,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathe matical  group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3695,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1829797,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":6491,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1836289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you unde rstood t he concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3171,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1839461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":4139,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1843601,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2361,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1845963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["english"],"rt":7871,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1853835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":4305,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1858141,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on  this HI T?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":[],"rt":1533,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1859675,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]